I'm an electrical contractor. I do $1.6 million a year.
My biggest constraint is myself plus hiring quality candidates.
If you have enough business, which it sounds like you do, that's not the constraint,
then it probably means we need a bump price.
And we bump price so that we can have the cash flow,
so that we can hire the extra person,
so that you have redundancy in the team.
I feel weird charging more
because other people in my market charge even less than I do,
and I'm a little bit above the market.
Then we have to think about the offer.
Can we make our thing faster?
Can we make it more reliable?
Or we can make it easier, right?
And can we guarantee around that?
And if the answer is yes, then it's like, great.
Well, then that's where we're going to charge our premium
and bump prices by 20 to 40 percent,
which sounds like a lot, I know.
We say, hey, if we don't meet any of these qualifications,
I'll give you all my profit back,
which means that you raise the price.
And if for some reason you don't meet it,
you go back to the exact same price you're charging now.
But everyone that you do meet everything on, you get all the juice.
You'll be able to increase the cash flow,
which will then allow you to go recruit the extra tech that you need
so you can stay above the business.
And then ultimately, honestly, just keep advertising it
so that you can keep hiring and backfilling.